I'm an industrial engineer.
[AI] 我是一名工业工程师。
The goal in my life has always been to make
[AI] 我生命中的目标一直是
more and more products
[AI] 越来越多的产品
in the least amount of time and resources.
[AI] 以最少的时间和资源。
While working at Toyota.
[AI] 在丰田工作期间。
all I knew was how to make cars
[AI] 我只知道如何制造汽车
until I met Dr. Akira Miyawaki.
[AI] 直到我见到宫崎骏博士。
who came to our factory to make a forest in it
[AI] 谁来我们工厂在里面建一片森林
in order to make it carbon-neutral.
[AI] 为了使其成为碳中和的。
I was so fascinated
[AI] 我太着迷了
that I decided to learn this methodology
[AI] 我决定学习这种方法
by joining his team as a volunteer.
[AI] 以志愿者的身份加入他的团队。
Soon. I started making a forest
[AI] 很快我开始建造一座森林
in the backyard of my own house.
[AI] 在我自己家的后院里。
and this is how it looks after three years.
[AI] 这就是三年后的情况。
These forests.
[AI] 这些森林。
compared to a conventional plantation.
[AI] 与传统种植园相比。
grow 10 times faster.
[AI] 增长快10倍。
they're 30 times more dense.
[AI] 它们的密度是原来的30倍。
and 100 times more biodiverse.
[AI] 是生物多样性的100倍。
Within two years of having this forest in our backyard.
[AI] 在我们后院拥有这片森林的两年内。
I could observe that the groundwater
[AI] 我可以观察到地下水
didn't dry during summers.
[AI] 夏天没有干燥。
the number of bird species I spotted in this area
[AI] 我在这个地区发现的鸟类数量
doubled.
[AI] 加倍。
Quality of air became better.
[AI] 空气质量有所改善。
and we started harvesting seasonal fruits
[AI] 我们开始收获季节性水果
growing effortlessly
[AI] 轻松成长
right in the backyard of our house.
[AI] 就在我家后院。
I wanted to make more of these forests.
[AI] 我想更多地利用这些森林。
I was so moved by these results
[AI] 我被这些结果感动了
that I wanted to make these forests
[AI] 我想建造这些森林
with the same acumen with which we make cars
[AI] 和我们制造汽车一样敏锐
or write software or do any mainstream business.
[AI] 或者写软件或者做任何主流业务。
so I founded a company
[AI] 于是我成立了一家公司
which is an end-to-end service provider
[AI] 这是一个端到端的服务提供商
to create these native natural forests.
[AI] 创造这些天然森林。
But to make afforestation as a mainstream business
[AI] 而是把植树造林作为一项主流业务
or an industry. we had to standardize
[AI] 或者一个行业。我们必须标准化
the process of forest-making.
[AI] 森林形成的过程。
So we benchmarked the Toyota Production System
[AI] 因此，我们对丰田生产系统进行了基准测试
known for its quality and efficiency
[AI] 以其质量和效率而闻名
for the process of forest-making.
[AI] 用于制作森林的过程。
For an example. the core of TPS.
[AI] 举个例子。TPS的核心。
Toyota Production System. lies in heijunka.
[AI] 丰田生产系统。位于平君卡。
which is making manufacturing
[AI] 这就是制造业
of different models of cars
[AI] 不同型号的汽车
on a single assembly line.
[AI] 在一条装配线上。
We replaced these cars with trees.
[AI] 我们把这些汽车换成了树。
using which now we can make multi-layered forests.
[AI] 现在我们可以用它来建造多层森林。
These forests utilize 100 percent vertical space.
[AI] 这些森林利用了100%的垂直空间。
They are so dense
[AI] 它们太密集了
that one can't even walk into them.
[AI] 那个人甚至不能走进他们。
For an example. we can make a 300-tree forest
[AI] 举个例子。我们可以造一个300棵树的森林
in an area as small as the parking spaces of six cars.
[AI] 在一个只有六辆车的停车位那么小的地方。
In order to reduce cost and our own carbon footprint.
[AI] 为了降低成本和我们自己的碳足迹。
we started utilizing local biomass
[AI] 我们开始利用当地的生物质
as soil amender and fertilizers.
[AI] 作为土壤改良剂和肥料。
For example. coconut shells crushed in a machine
[AI] 例如椰子壳被机器压碎
mixed with rice straw.
[AI] 和稻草混合。
powder of rice husk mixed with organic manure
[AI] 混合有机肥料的稻壳粉
is finally dumped in soil on which
[AI] 最终被倾倒在土壤中
our forest is planted.
[AI] 我们的森林被种植了。
Once planted. we use grass or rice straw
[AI] 一旦种植。我们用草或稻草
to cover the soil
[AI] 覆土
so that all the water which goes into irrigation
[AI] 因此，所有进入灌溉的水
doesn't get evaporated back into the atmosphere.
[AI] 不会蒸发回大气中。
And using these simple improvisations.
[AI] 用这些简单的即兴表演。
today we can make a forest
[AI] 今天我们可以建造一座森林
for a cost as low as the cost of an iPhone.
[AI] 价格和iPhone一样便宜。
Today. we are making forests in houses.
[AI] 今天我们正在房屋中建造森林。
in schools. even in factories with the corporates.
[AI] 在学校里。甚至在有公司的工厂里。
But that's not enough.
[AI] 但这还不够。
There is a huge number of people
[AI] 有很多人
who want to take matters into their own hands.
[AI] 他们想把事情掌握在自己手中。
So we let it happen.
[AI] 所以我们让它发生。
Today. we are working on an Internet-based platform
[AI] 今天我们正在一个基于互联网的平台上工作
where we are going to share our methodology
[AI] 我们将在哪里分享我们的方法
on an open source
[AI] 关于开源
using which anyone and everyone
[AI] 任何人和每个人都在使用它
can make their own forest
[AI] 他们可以建造自己的森林
without our physical presence being there.
[AI] 没有我们的存在。
using our methodology.
[AI] 使用我们的方法。
At the click of a button.
[AI] 点击一个按钮。
they can get to know all the native species
[AI] 他们可以了解所有的本地物种
of their place.
[AI] 他们的位置。
By installing a small hardware probe on site.
[AI] 通过在现场安装一个小型硬件探头。
we can do remote soil testing.
[AI] 我们可以做远程土壤测试。
using which we can give step-by-step instructions
[AI] 使用它我们可以给出一步一步的说明
on forest-making remotely.
[AI] 关于森林建设。
Also we can monitor the growth of this forest
[AI] 我们还可以监测这片森林的生长情况
without being on site.
[AI] 不在现场。
This methodology. I believe.
[AI] 这种方法。我相信。
has a potential.
[AI] 有潜力。
By sharing. we can actually
[AI] 通过分享。实际上我们可以
bring back our native forests.
Now. when you go back home.
if you see a barren piece of land.
do remember that it can be a potential forest.
Thank you very much. Thanks.
(Applause)